威尔 · 森特斯: 我认为这是美好时刻的范围
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: I think this is
the scope of nice moment to see
现在越来越标准的做法。
the increasingly more standard
way of doing this nowadays.
使用这个特性的新方法来定义或声明
That uses this feature of a new
way of defining or declaring or
在 JavaScript 中保存函数，我们昨天看到的。
saving functions in JavaScript
that we saw yesterday.
这就是我们的箭头函数风格。
Which was our arrow function style.
因为我们的箭头函数样式，声明或
Cuz our arrow function style,
of declaring or
保存功能，将句子: 自动,
saving functions,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Automatically,
我现在要告诉你们，这是词汇学上的范围。
I'm gonna tell you right now,
is lexically scoped.
这意味着我们保存函数的地方，或者，让我明确一下，不，对不起。
That means where we save the function or,
let me set that clear on that, no, sorry.
这个作业的词汇范围。
Is, it's this assignment
is lexically scoped.
也就是说，当我们保存函数时，当我们执行它时,
That is to say, when we save the function,
when we execute it,
它的设置取决于函数保存的位置。
what this is set to is determined
by where the function was saved.
所以如果它保存在用户1的位置，当我们最终运行它时,
So if it was saved where this is user 1,
when we end up running it,
内部的这个值就是函数保存的位置，也就是 User1。
this inside will be this value from where
the function was saved, which is User1.
让我们看看这个例子。
So let's just see that example here.
我们现在已经定义了一个箭头函数，让我们做一个小小的改变。
We've defined in now with an arrow
function, let's make this slight change.
让我们一起快速执行它，再一次，确保我们已经得到它。
Let's quickly execute it together,
one more time, make sure we've got it.
让我们再快速地执行一次，所以我们在这里执行。
Let's quickly execute it one more time,
so we're executing here.
这些都是小小的错综复杂，但是
These are little intricacies here, but
我想给大家带来一些有趣的附加信息。
little fun bonus bits I wanted
to include for you all.
所以我们正在运行 user1.increment。
So we're running user1.increment.
它通过 user1从函数存储中运行增量方法。
It runs the increment method
from function store via user1.
我说过你很快就会过去的。
I said you go through that quickly.
1.increment，user1 is in？
Dan, user1.increment, user1 is in?
讲者2: 全局存储器。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Global memory.
句子: 全局内存，我们寻找增量的方法，它在那里吗？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Global memory, we look
for the increment method, is it there?
演讲者2: 没有，所以我们进入原型，然后
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Nope, so
we go to the proto, and
让我找到它在用户函数应该存储对象。
let me find it in the user
function should store object.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 太棒了，我们拿到了它的代码，然后我们想执行它。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Fantastic, we grab
its code, and we thought executing it.
第一件事和本地记忆丹是什么？
And the first thing and
local memory Dan is?
演讲者2: 常数在1，这。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Constant at 1, this.
是的，作为一个参数，没有问题，是什么？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah,
as a parameter, no problem, which is?
讲者2: 用户1 威尔 · 森塔斯: 这是什么
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: User1.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Which is what
我们希望如此，因为我们正在运行这个函数
we hope because that's what
we're running this function
我们希望这会影响到。
owns that we hope it's
going to affect this.
我们总是希望拥有自己的功能和数据。
We always wanna have our functionality and
our data.
能够直接在数据上使用该功能
Able to use the functionality
directly on the data right there and
这就是我们的目的。
then that's the kind of
the whole goal of this.
所以不要忘记，当我们进入这些错综复杂的
So don't forget that as we go
into these intricacies and
别忘了总体目标。
don't forget that overall goal.
这是一个多么美妙的好看。
This is what a fantastic looking good.
我们来声明这个函数 Dan。
Let's declare that function Dan.
讲者2:1及。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: At 1 and.
威尔 · 句子: 在箭头函数星中，它没有什么不同。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: In the arrow
function star, but it's no different.
就是这个。
There it is.
然后我们马上用它做什么，丹？
And we immediately do what with it, Dan?
演讲者2: 我们称之为执行。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: We call it, e execute it.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 我们称之为执行。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: We call it,
e execute it.
全新的什么，丹？
Brand new what, Dan?
演讲者2: 有点像执行。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Execution kinda.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 执行是美丽的，在它的本地记忆里。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Execution beautiful,
and in it's local memory.
因为它是一个箭头函数。
Because it's an arrow function.
我不知道，我认为我们需要它，它在我们的职能。
I don't know, I though we necessitated it,
it's in our function.
它是局部内存中的这个分配，它是全局的吗,
It's this assignment inside the local
memory, will it be global because note,
我们的一个简单规则是，任何运行在右手边的函数
our one simple rule is any function
that's being run to the right hand side
不管左手边是什么，那就是列表赋值。
of the dot whatever the left hand side
that's going to be the list assignment.
但是当这里没有点的时候，它将全局默认为窗口。
But when there's no dot here,
it defaults the global to the window.
除非该函数被定义为箭头函数,
Unless that function was
defined as an arrow function,
在这种情况下，丹，我们的这个任务将是什么？
in which case Dan our this
assignment will be what?
演讲者2: 用户1 still。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: User1 still.
Will Sentance: 用户一，围绕定义的这个任务到底是什么
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: User one, exactly what
was this assignment around the definition
其中的1在词典上是作用域。
of that 1 is lexically scoped.
它静止的范围，这个任务。
It staticly the scope, this assignment.
这是一个静态的或词汇上的这个作业，也就是说它来自
It's a statically or lexically this
assignment, that is to say it's from
定义的那一刻，我们把它设置为 User1。
the moment of definition that
we set our this to User1.
因此，我们的代码行 this.score 加上,
Therefore, our line of
code this.score plus plus,
会怎么评估 Todd 呢？
is going to evaluate to what Todd, now?
讲者2: User1.score + + 。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: User1.score++.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 太棒了，user1.score + + 。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Fantastic,
user1.score++.
你得再上几层楼。
You gotta go a few levels out.
1,2,3，这是我们的分数财产。
1, 2, 3, there's our score property.
它会增加到4，让我们把它增加到,
It would increment to four but,
let's increment it to,
威尔 · 森塔斯: 5，神奇的人们。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: 5, fantastic people.
现在我认为这是一个很好的方法来解决这个问题
This now I think is a nice way
of solving this problem for
写下这些干净的代码。
writing this clean code here.
好了，各位，现在我们从拇指开始
All right people, let's have to
start with thumbs here at this point
有没有人想加点大拇指什么的尽管说吧 Peter。
on any of those bonus pieces anyone want
to add any thumbs, yeah, go ahead Peter.
说话人2: 是否声明增量
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Would
declaring the increment
作为一个箭头功能，以及帮助我们呢？
property as an arrow
function as well help us?
威尔 · 森塔斯: 但是会吗？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Would it though?
因为如果我们这样做，当我们运行增量时。
Because if we did so,
when we ran that increment.
所以彼得的问题是，如果我们把增量当作一个箭头函数呢？
So Peter's question there is what if we
say an increment as an arrow function?
如果我们运行它，这个分配是否取决于它在哪里运行
If we ran it, would it's this assignment
be determined by where it's being run
点的右边还是存储位置，在全局数据库里？
to the right hand side of the dot or by
where it was stored, which was in global?
因此，整个系统就会崩溃。
By where it was stored, and therefore
the whole thing would fall apart.
现在，这将不是 User1。
And now this will not be User1.
所以我们不想使用包含的箭头函数
So we don't want to use arrow
functions for our include for
我们对物体的方法。
our methods on objects.
但是对于它们内部的函数，我们要指出这一点
But for the functions inside of them
that we want to have point there this to
他们被定义的方法，完美无缺。
the method in which they were defined,
perfect.